http://www.naspa.com/privacy-statement

QUICK JOB SEARCH/
Join NaSPA/Membership LevelsAssociates & StudentsCurrent & Former MilitaryBasic MembersFull Voting MembersCorporate MembersLifetime Members
QUICK JOB SEARCH/
Join NaSPA/Membership LevelsAssociates & StudentsCurrent & Former MilitaryBasic MembersFull Voting MembersCorporate MembersLifetime Members
Log In/
NaSPA has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy and the confidentiality of our members.INFORMATION COLLECTIONWe will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (Personal Information) or allows us to contact you. Generally this information is requested when you are asked to register as a member or to enter a limited-access site.  We use a member ID number, an assigned site member name, and a password chosen by our members to permit them access to our restricted membership services. Once registered, our members have the option of obtaining a digital certificate to be used to control this access. We use your IP address as recorded in our site logs only as needed to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Site usage information is not analyzed for other purposes or shared with other sites.COOKIESWe may use temporary cookies to save access permissions for our members so that they do not have to log in multiple times as they attempt to access restricted pages during a single online session. These cookies expire after a limited time, do not contain any personal information, and are not shared with any other web site.PERSONAL INFORMATIONOur site's on-line membership registration form requires users to give us contact information (such as name and email address), and accepts credit card information for membership processing. This information is used to contact members and to provide membership services. As soon as possible, we intend to accept membership applications and renewals over the Internet through a secured SSL link. All personal and credit information submitted for this purpose are not stored upon the web server, and so are protected from misuse.On occasion we use the member contact information to provide special educational opportunities and other benefits to our members. By choice, we prefer to do all such mailings ourselves. When it is necessary to share this information with other organizations with whom we are partnered, we do so only with an agreement that they are to be used a single time and for a specific purpose. The mailing and the mailing list are then sent to an independent mailing house to be sent out via bulk mail. E-mail is never used as a part of this process, and the purchasing organization does not ever see the mailing list. On occasion, we will also sell our mailing list to other computer organizations as a means of raising revenues. The same process is used for these mailings.CONSENTWe understand that some individuals prefer not to have their personal information, including their contact information, used for any other purposes whatsoever. As a member, if you do not want your personal information used for purposes other than strictly NaSPA organization business, you can also contact NASPA at 1 (262) 67-NASPA.
Home/
About NaSPA/
QUICK JOB SEARCH/
Join NaSPA/Membership LevelsAssociates & StudentsCurrent & Former MilitaryBasic MembersFull Voting MembersCorporate MembersLifetime Members
Gift NaSPA/
Publications/
Advertise/
Sponsor/
Contact/
Log In/
NASPA
NaSPA, a non-profit corporation, fosters a greater respect for network, mainframe, I.T., telecommunications, business continuity, and other professionals, while it improves employment and educational opportunities for thousands of technologists worldwide.
Thumb Drive OfferOver 4000 Issues of NaSPA Publications and contains Linux Mint and other utilities!
Enjoy 30% naspa discount with cisco press using coupon code: techsupport
©2020 NaSPA Inc.  |  Home  |  Join  |  Cancellation Policy  |  Privacy Statement  |  Legal DisclaimerNetwork and Systems Professionals Association  |  Dallas Number (214) 771-8616  |  Milwaukee Number (262) 67-NASPA
Login
Welcome, (First Name)!
Forgot?
Show
Stay Logged In
Log In
Enter Member Area
(Message automatically replaces this text)
OK
My Profile
Log Out
